Contact

umesh.rgpv@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/umeshmotwani-59723236 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java

Agile Methodologies

Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Certifications

Oracle Certified Professional, Java SE 6 Programmer

Oracle Certified Professional, Java SE 6 Programmer

Umesh Motwani

Senior Consultant - Software Engineering at Slalom New York City Metropolitan Area

Summary

With over 12 years of experience as a Software Engineer, I have collaborated with various clients in roles such as Solutions Architect, Full Stack Developer and Al Engineer, providing my expertise in designing, developing, and maintaining enterprise-level web applications. My goal is to partner with Product Managers, Subject Matter Experts, and end users to develop functionalities that align with business objectives while adhering to best practices and industry standards.

Certifications include:

- GCP Certified Solutions Architect Professional
- AWS Certified Architect-Associate
- AWS Certified Developer
- AWS Certified Machine Learning Specialty
- Azure Fundamentals Certified
- Oracle certified web developer

Experience

Slalom

5 years 9 months

Senior Consultant - Software Engineering July 2021 - Present (3 years 11 months) Newyork

Software Engineer

September 2019 - July 2021 (1 year 11 months)

New York

Tata Consultancy Services

8 years

AWS Architect

November 2017 - September 2019 (1 year 11 months)

Newark, New Jersey

Full Stack Developer August 2016 - October 2017 (1 year 3 months) United States

Java Developer October 2011 - August 2016 (4 years 11 months) Mumbai Area, India

Education

Rajiv Gandhi Prodyogiki Vishwavidyalaya

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Science · (2007 - 2011)